A Guide to the Register of Regulations records of the Virginia Code Commission, 1937-2021.
Library of Virginia
- Register of Regulations records, 1937-2021.
  - Accession 52837 (1953-2016, 33 cubic feet).
    - Child Day-Care Council, 2004-2014. (Box 30)
    - Dept. for the Deaf and Hard of Hearing, 2009. (Box 30)
    - Board for Protection and Advocacy, 2009-2014. (Box 30)
    - Dept. of Aging and Rehabilitative Services, 2005-2012. (Box 30)
    - Dept. of Social Services, 1988-2016. (Box 30)
    - Dept. of Social Services, 1992-2017. (Box 31)
    - Dept. for the Blind and Visually Impaired, 1990-2016. (Box 31)
    - Dept. of Taxation, 1985-2016. (Box 31)
    - Virginia Aviation Board, 2011. (Box 31)
    - State Corporation Commission - Div. of Utility and Railroad Safety, 1990-2013. (Box 31)
    - Dept. of Motor Vehicles, 1985-2013. (Box 31)
    - Motor Vehicle Dealer Board, 1997-2007. (Box 31)
    - Board of Towing and Recovery Operations, 2008-2013. (Box 31)
    - Dept. of Transportation, 1994-2016. (Box 31)
    - Commission on the Virginia Alcohol Safety Action Program, 2008. (Box 31)
    - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 2016-2017. (Box 32)
    - Marine Resources Commission, 2016-2018. (Box 32)
    - Dept. of Criminal Justice Services, undated. (Box 32)
    - Virginia Waste Management Board, 2017. (Box 32)
    - State Water Control Board, 2017. (Box 32)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 2015-2018. (Box 32)
    - Board of Audiology and Speech-Language Pathology, 2017. (Box 32)
    - Common Interest Community Board, 2017. (Box 32)
    - Board of Optometry, 2017. (Box 32)
    - Board of Nursing, 2017. (Box 32)
    - Board of Pharmacy, 2017-2018. (Box 32)
    - Board of Veterinary Medicine, 2017. (Box 32)
    - Dept. of Fire Programs, 1987. (Box 32)
    - Human Rights Council, 1990. (Box 32)
    - Dept. of Social Services, 2018. (Box 32)
    - Dept. of Taxation, 1982-2016. (Box 32)
    - Dept. of Transportation, 1990-2015. (Box 32)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development (DIBR), 2006-2012. (Box 33)
    - State Corporation Commission (DIBR), 2011. (Box 33)
  - Accession 53907 (1958-2021, 90 cubic feet).
    Finding aid includes the the names of the agencies or boards included in each box. For file inventory for this accession, see: Detailed Folder Listing (53907).
    - Virginia Waste Management Board, 1986-2003. (Box 1)
    - Virginia Waste Management Board, 1986-2003. (Box 2)
    - Virginia Waste Management Board, 1988-1999. (Box 3)
    - State Water Control Board, 1988-1999. (Box 3)
    - State Water Control Board, 1975-2002. (Box 4)
    - Dept. of Elections, 1972-2005. (Box 5)
    - Dept. of Education, 1972-2005. (Box 5)
    - Dept. of Health, 1984-2005. (Box 6)
    - State Water Control Board, 1976-2002. (Box 7)
    - Virginia Waste Management Board, 1985-1999. (Box 8)
    - State Water Control Board, 1975-2010. (Box 9)
    - Dept. of Health, 1975-2010. (Box 9)
    - State Water Control Board, 1992-2003. (Box 10)
    - Dept. of Heatlh, 1971-2002. (Box 11)
    - Dept. of Health, 1978-2008. (Box 12)
    - Dept. of Health, 1979-2005. (Box 13)
    - State Water Control Board, 1976-2003. (Box 14)
    - Dept. of Health, 1970-1993. (Box 15)
    - Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1987-2010. (Box 16)
    - State Water Control Board, 1975-1992. (Box 17)
    - Board of Nursing, 1974-2008. (Box 18)
    - Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1977-2006. (Box 19)
    - State Water Control Board, 1972-1994. (Box 20)
    - Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1988-2003. (Box 21)
    - Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1984-2011. (Box 22)
    - State Lottery, 1984-2011. (Box 22)
    - Virginia Manufactured Housing Board, 1984-2011. (Box 22)
    - Board of Nursing, 1980-2008. (Box 23)
    - Dept. of Juvenile Justice, 1980-2008. (Box 23)
    - Dept. of Health, 1967-1991. (Box 24)
    - Dept. of Labor and Industy, 1981-2009. (Box 25)
    - State Lottery, 1969-2004. (Box 26)
    - Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1969-2004. (Box 26)
    - Dept. of Labor and Industry, 1969-2004. (Box 26)
    - State Water Control Board, 1974-1993. (Box 27)
    - Dept. of Labor and Industry, 1974-1997. (Box 28)
    - State Water Control Board, 1971-1994. (Box 29)
    - State Water Control Board, 1971-1994. (Box 30)
    - Dept. of Motor Vehicles, 1971-1994. (Box 30)
    - Safety and Health Codes Board, 1976-2007. (Box 31)
    - Board of Medicine, 1978-2008. (Box 32)
    - Safety and Health Codes Board, 1978-1999. (Box 33)
    - Board of Medicine, 1980-2009. (Box 34)
    - Dept. of Taxation, 1979-2009. (Box 35)
    - Board for Professional Soil Scientists and Wetlands Professionals, 1979-2009. (Box 35)
    - Board of Medicine, 1976-2009. (Box 36)
    - Board of Psychology, 1976-2009. (Box 36)
    - Dept. of Social Services, 1976-2009. (Box 36)
    - Dept. of Motor Vehicles, 1972-2008. (Box 37)
    - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1972-2008. (Box 37)
    - Virginia Museum of Fine Art, 1972-2008. (Box 37)
    - Virginia Parole Board, 1972-2008. (Box 37)
    - Board of Physical Therapy, 1972-2008. (Box 37)
    - Dept. of Taxation, 1982-2000. (Box 38)
    - Dept. for the Deaf and Hard of Hearing, 1979-2010. (Box 39)
    - Dept. of Social Services, 1979-2010. (Box 39)
    - Dept. of Mines, Minerals and Energy, 1977-2011. (Box 40)
    - Board of Long Term Care Administrators, 1965-2008. (Box 41)
    - Board for Opticians; Board of Optometry, 1965-2008. (Box 41)
    - Board of Medicine, 1965-2008. (Box 41)
    - Board of Social Services, 1986-2012. (Box 42)
    - Board of Pharmacy, 1975-2009. (Box 43)
    - Board of Optometry, 1975-2009. (Box 43)
    - Board of Nursing, 1975-2009. (Box 43)
    - Dept. of Taxation, 1971-1979. (Box 44)
    - Dept. of Mines, Minerals and Energy, 1973-2004. (Box 45)
    - Dept. of Social Services, 1987-2011. (Box 46)
    - Board of Psychology, 1972-2010. (Box 47)
    - Virginia Racing Commission, 1977-2009. (Box 48)
    - Real Estate Board, 1977-2009. (Box 48)
    - Real Estate Board, 1978-2009. (Box 49)
    - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, 1972-2010. (Box 50)
    - Dept. of Taxation, 1970-1997. (Box 51)
    - Dept. of Social Services, 1983-2007. (Box 52)
    - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, 1985-2008. (Box 53)
    - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services; State Milk Commission; Virginia Health Planning Board; Council on Human Rights, 1973-2008. (Box 54)
    - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, 1973-2008. (Box 54)
    - State Milk Commission, 1973-2008. (Box 54)
    - Virginia Health Planning Board, 1973-2008. (Box 54)
    - Council on Human Rights, 1973-2008. (Box 54)
    - Dept. of Social Services, 1980-2003. (Box 55)
    - Dept. of Social Services, 1986-2009. (Box 56)
    - Dept. of Social Services, 1975-1999. (Box 57)
    - Dept. of Social Services, 1975-2000. (Box 58)
    - Dept. of Transportation, 1989-2000. (Box 59)
    - Dept. of Transportation, 1983-2011. (Box 60)
    - Dept. of Social Services, 1975-1999. (Box 61)
    - Dept. of Social Services, 1988-2001. (Box 62)
    - Dept. of State Police, 1988-2001. (Box 62)
    - Dept. of Transportation, 1978-2012. (Box 63)
    - Dept. of Mines, Minerals and Energy, 1979-1994. (Box 64)
    - Dept. of Mines, Minerals and Energy, 1981-2008. (Box 65)
    - Dept. of Motor Vehicles, 1981-2008. (Box 65)
    - Board for Waterworks and Wastewater Works Operators, 1981-2008. (Box 65)
    - Board for Waste Management Facility Operators, 1981-2008. (Box 65)
    - Dept. of Transportation, 1958-1987. (Box 66)
    - Dept. of Transportation, 1972-1994. (Box 67)
    - Virginia Indigent Defense Commission, 1972-1994. (Box 67)
    - Office of the Adjutant General, 1972-1994. (Box 67)
    - Board of Veterinary Medicine, 1972-2005. (Box 68)
    - Dept. Conservation and Recreation, 1979-1995. (Box 69)
    - Dept. of Health, 1979-1995. (Box 69)
    - Dept. of Social Services, 1979-1995. (Box 69)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1979-1995. (Box 69)
    - Dept. of Environmental Quality, 1980-1999. (Box 70)
    - Dept. of Health, 1980-1999. (Box 70)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1977-1989. (Box 71)
    - Virginia Retirement System, 1977-1989. (Box 71)
    - Dept. of Planning and Budget, 1977-1989. (Box 71)
    - Radford University, 1977-1989. (Box 71)
    - Virginia Community College System, 1977-1989. (Box 71)
    - Dept. of Transportation, 1973-1997. (Box 72)
    - Dept. of Elections, 2010-2020. (Box 73)
    - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 2010-2020. (Box 73)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control Authority, 2010-2020. (Box 73)
    - Dept. of Conservation and Recreation, 2010-2020. (Box 73)
    - Dept. of Wildlife Resources, 2010-2020. (Box 73)
    - Marine Resources Commission, 2010-2020. (Box 73)
    - State Air Pollution Control Board, 2010-2020. (Box 73)
    - Waste Management Board, 2010-2020. (Box 73)
    - Virginia Racing Commission, 2010-2020. (Box 73)
    - Dept. of Health, 2010-2020. (Box 73)
    - Dept. of Education, 2010-2020. (Box 73)
    - State Water Control Board, 2010-2020. (Box 73)
    - Dept. Medical Assistance Services, 2010-2020. (Box 73)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1972-1985. (Box 74)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1974-1995. (Box 75)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1980-1994. (Box 76)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1978-1995. (Box 77)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1974-1994. (Box 78)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1982-1993. (Box 79)
    - Marine Resources Commission, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Real Estate Appraiser Board, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - State Corporation Commission, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Virginia State Bar, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Dept. of Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Virginia Housing Development Authority, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Safety and Health Codes Board, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Board for Asbestos, Lead and Home Inspectors, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Common Interest Community Board, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Board for Contractors, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Board of Dentistry, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Board of Pharmacy, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Board of Counseling, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Board of Psychology, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Real Estate Board, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Board of Social Work, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Dept. of Fire Programs, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Board for Waterworks and Wastewater Works Operators and Onsite Sewage System Professionals, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Dept. of State Police, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - State Corporation Commission, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Dept. for Aging and Rehabilitative Services, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Dept. of Transportation, 2016-2021. (Box 80)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development - DIBR, 2011-2015. (Box 81)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development - DIBR, 2016-2020. (Box 82)
    - State Board of Elections, 2016-2020. (Box 82)
    - Dept. of General Services, 2016-2020. (Box 82)
    - Office of the State Inspector General, 2016-2020. (Box 82)
    - Dept. of Law, 2016-2020. (Box 82)
    - Commission on Local Government, 2016-2020. (Box 82)
    - Dept. of Veterans Services, 2016-2020. (Box 82)
    - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 2016-2020. (Box 82)
    - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1997-2020. (Box 83)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control Authority, 1997-2020. (Box 83)
    - Dept. of Wildlife Resources, 1997-2020. (Box 83)
    - Marine Resources Commission, 1997-2020. (Box 83)
    - Dept. of Energy, 1997-2020. (Box 83)
    - State Corporation Commission, 1997-2020. (Box 83)
    - State Board of Local and Regional Jails, 1997-2020. (Box 83)
    - rDept. of Criminal Justice Services, 1997-2020. (Box 83)
    - State Board of Education, 1997-2020. (Box 83)
    - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia, 1997-2020. (Box 83)
    - Norfolk State University, 1997-2020. (Box 83)
    - University of Virginia, 1997-2020. (Box 83)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1997-2020. (Box 83)
    - Virginia State University, 1997-2020. (Box 83)
    - College of William and Mary, 1997-2020. (Box 83)
    - State Air Pollution Control Board, 1997-2020. (Box 83)
    - State Air Pollution Control Board, 1993-2020. (Box 84)
    - State Board of Education, 1993-2020. (Box 84)
    - Virginia Waste Management Board, 1993-2020. (Box 84)
    - State Water Control Board, 1993-2020. (Box 84)
    - Safety and Health Codes Board, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Virginia Workers' Compensation Commission, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Board of Accountancy, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Board for Asbestos, Lead and Home Inspectors, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Board of Audiology and Speech-Language Pathology, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Cemetery Board, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Common Interest Community Board, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Board for Contractors, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Board of Dentistry, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Board of Funeral Directors and Embalmers, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Dept. of Health Professions, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Board for Hearing Aid Specialists and Opticians, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Board of Medicine, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Board of Nursing, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Board of Optometry, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Board of Pharmacy, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Board of Physical Therapy, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Board of Counseling, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Board of Psychology, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Real Estate Appraiser Board, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Real Estate Board, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Board of Social Work, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Board of Veterinary Medicine, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Board for Waterworks and Wastewater Works Operators and Onsite Sewage System Professionals, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Dept. of State Police, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - State Corporation Commission, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Dept. for Aging and Rehabilitative Services, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Dept. of Social Services, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Dept. of Taxation, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Dept. of Transportation, 2016-2020. (Box 85)
    - Dept. of Health, 2016-2020. (Box 86)
    - Dept. of Behavioural Health and Developmental Services, 2016-2020. (Box 86)
    - State Water Control Board, 2016-2020. (Box 87)
    - State Corporation Commission, 2016-2020. (Box 87)
    - Virginia Racing Commission, 2016-2020. (Box 87)
    - Charitable Gaming Board, 2016-2020. (Box 87)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 2016-2020. (Box 87)
    - Virginia Manufactured Housing Board, 2016-2020. (Box 87)
    - Virginia Housing Development Authority, 2016-2020. (Box 87)
    - Virginia Birth-Related Neurological Injury Compensation Program, 2016-2020. (Box 87)
    - Dept. of Labor and Industry, 2016-2020. (Box 87)
    - Apprenticeship Council, 2016-2020. (Box 87)
    - Safety and Health Codes Board, 2016-2020. (Box 87)
    - Virginia Workers' Compensation Commission, 2016-2020. (Box 87)
    - Board of Historic Resources, 2016-2020. (Box 87)
    - Dept. of Historic Resources, 2016-2020. (Box 87)
    - Board of Accountancy, 2016-2020. (Box 87)
    - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2016-2020. (Box 87)
    - Board for Asbestos, Lead and Home Inspectors, 2016-2020. (Box 87)
    - Auctioneers Board, 2016-2020. (Box 87)
    - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Virginia Alcoholic Beverage Control Authority, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Dept. of Wildlife Resources, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Dept. of Forensic Science, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - State Board of Education, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - State Water Control Board, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - State Corporation Commission, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Virginia Racing Commission, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Dept. of Health, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Dept. of Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers, and Landscape Architects, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Common Interest Community Board, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Board of Dentistry, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Board of Funeral Directors and Embalmers, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Board for Hearing Aid Specialists and Opticians, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Board of Nursing, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Board of Pharmacy, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Board of Physical Therapy, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Board of Psychology, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Board for Waterworks and Wastewater Works Operators and Onsite Sewage System Professionals, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Dept. for Aging and Rehabilitateve Services, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Dept. of Social Services, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - State Board of Elections, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Dept. of Wildlife Resources, 2016-2020. (Box 88)
    - Board of Audiology and Speech-Language Pathology, 2010-2020. (Box 89)
    - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2010-2020. (Box 89)
    - Board for Branch Pilots, 2010-2020. (Box 89)
    - Cemetery Board, 2010-2020. (Box 89)
    - Common Interest Community Board, 2010-2020. (Box 89)
    - Board for Barbers, 2010-2020. (Box 89)
    - Dept. of State Police, 2010-2020. (Box 89)
    - State Corporation Commission, 2010-2020. (Box 89)
    - Dept. for Aging and Rehabilitative Services, 2010-2020. (Box 89)
    - Dept. of Social Services, 2010-2020. (Box 89)
    - Dept. for the Blind and Vision Impaired, 2010-2020. (Box 89)
    - Dept. of Taxation, 2010-2020. (Box 89)
    - Dept. of Transportation, 2010-2020. (Box 89)
    - Commission on the Virginia Alcohol Safety Action Program, 2010-2020. (Box 89)
    - Board of Dentistry, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
    - Board for Contractors, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
    - Fair Housing Board, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
    - Board for Funeral Directors and Embalmers, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
    - Board of Health Professions, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
    - Dept. of Health Professions, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
    - Board for Hearing Aid Specialists and Opticians, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
    - Board of Medicine, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
    - Board of Nursing, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
    - Board of Optometry, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
    - Board of Long-Term Care Administrators, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
    - Board of Pharmacy, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
    - Board of Physical Therapy, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
    - Real Estate Appraiser Board, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
    - Real Estate Board, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
    - Board of Social Work, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
    - Board of Professional Soil Scientists, Wetland Professionals, and Geologists, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
    - Board of Veterinary Medicine, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
    - Board for Waste Management Facility Operators, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
    - Board for Waterworks and Wastewater Works Operators and Onsite Sewage System Professionals, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
    - Virginia Birth-Related Neurological Injury Compensation Program, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
    - State Air Pollution Control Board, 2016-2020. (Box 90)
  - Accession 53993 (1970-2020, 5 cubic feet).
    Finding aid includes the the names of the agencies or boards included in each box. For file inventory for this accession, see: Detailed Folder Listing (53993).
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board - Correspondence, 1976-1992. (Box 1)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board - Regulatory review, 1994-2019. (Box 1)
    - Virginia Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Correspondence, 1975-2003. (Box 1)
    - Virginia Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Regulatory review, 1979-2019. (Box 1)
    - Virginia Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services - Notices, 1976-1993. (Box 1)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts - Correspondence, 1978-1994. (Box 1)
    - State Air Pollution Board - Correspondence, 1979-1999. (Box 1)
    - State Air Pollution Board - Regulatory review, 2002-2020. (Box 1)
    - Attorney General, Office of the - Correspondence, 1979-1994. (Box 1)
    - Audiology and Speech Language Pathology, Board of - Regulatory review, 2018. (Box 1)
    - Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1975-1994. (Box 1)
    - Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Dept. of - Regulatory review, 1996-2020. (Box 1)
    - Accountancy, Board of - Correspondence, 1977-2009. (Box 1)
    - Counseling, Board of - Regulatory review, 2000-2018. (Box 1)
    - Housing, Board of - Correspondence, 1975-1977. (Box 1)
    - Medicine, Board of - Correspondence, 1976-2011. (Box 1)
    - Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance - Regulatory review, 1995-2002. (Box 1)
    - Community College System, Virginia - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 1)
    - Child Day Care Council - Correspondence, 2008. (Box 1)
    - Cemetery Board - Regulatory review, 2012-2019. (Box 1)
    - Human Rights Council - Correspondence, 1989-2009. (Box 1)
    - Criminal Justice Services, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1970-2017. (Box 1)
    - Local Government - Correspondence, 1984-2019. (Box 1)
    - Local Government - Regulatory review, 1994-2017. (Box 1)
    - Comptroller, Office of the / Dept. of Accounts - Correspondence, 1972-1994. (Box 1)
    - Certified Seed Board - Correspondence, 1990. (Box 1)
    - Correctional Education, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1994. (Box 1)
    - Charitable Gaming - Correspondence, 1996-2018. (Box 1)
    - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1978-2005. (Box 2)
    - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of - Regulatory review, 1994-1995. (Box 2)
    - Emergency Management Services, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1975-1994. (Box 2)
    - Environmental Quality, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1977-2009. (Box 2)
    - Environmental Quality, Dept. of - Regulatory review, 1995-2019. (Box 2)
    - Fire Programs, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1987-2004. (Box 2)
    - Forensic Science Board - Regulatory review, 2017. (Box 2)
    - General Services, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1984-2020. (Box 2)
    - Deaf and Hard of Hearing, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1986-1992. (Box 2)
    - Deaf and Hard of Hearing, Dept. of - Regulatory review, 1994-2006. (Box 2)
    - Health Professions, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1977-1996. (Box 2)
    - Health Professions, Dept. of - Regulatory review, 1994-2006. (Box 2)
    - Historic Resources, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1995-2020. (Box 2)
    - Technology Planning, Dept. of - Regulatory review, 1994-2016. (Box 2)
    - Juvenile Justice, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1997-2009. (Box 2)
    - Juvenile Justice, Dept. of - Regulatory review, 1998-2019. (Box 2)
    - Military Affairs, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1991-1995. (Box 2)
    - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1975-2009. (Box 2)
    - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of - Regulatory review, 1994-2019. (Box 2)
    - Dentistry, Board of - Correspondence, 1973-2018. (Box 2)
    - Accounts, Dept. of, 1970-2020. (Box 2)
    - Corrections, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1994-2011. (Box 2)
    - Education, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1973-2011. (Box 2)
    - Forestry, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1985-2012. (Box 2)
    - Transportation, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1975-2011. (Box 2)
    - Transportation, Dept. of - Regulatory review, 1974-2020. (Box 2)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of - Correspondence, 1987-1994. (Box 2)